<resources>
    <string name="app_name" translatable="false">PA OVR APP</string>

    <string name="no_intent_handler" translatable="false">
        There are no applications available to handle this action.
    </string>

    <string name="navigation_label_previous">previous</string>
    <string name="navigation_label_next">next</string>

    <!--Nav Drawer Strings-->
    <string name="nav_title_home" translatable="false">Home</string>
    <string name="nav_title_about" translatable="false">About</string>
    <string name="nav_title_data_usage" translatable="false">Data Usage</string>
    <string name="nav_title_help" translatable="false">Help</string>
    <string name="incomplete_profile_alert">Some of your canvasser information is incomplete. You must enter your name, Partner ID, Event ID and Event Zip before registering voters</string>
    <string name="dialog_no_thanks">No Thanks</string>
    <string name="dialog_enter_info">Enter Info</string>

    <!--Main Activity Strings-->
    <string name="label_total_registered" translatable="false">Total Registered</string>
    <string name="label_registered_event">Registered</string>
    <string name="button_label_new_voter" translatable="false">New Voter</string>
    <string name="event_details" translatable="false">Event Details</string>
    <string name="error_partner_id" translatable="false">Invalid Partner ID</string>
    <string name="label_partner_name_spinner">Validating Partner ID</string>

    <!--Registration Activity Strings-->
    <string name="cancel_dialog_message">Cancel current registration?</string>
    <string name="dialog_yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="dialog_no">No</string>

    <!--Eligibility Fragment Strings-->
    <string name="fragment_title_new_registrant">Name</string>
    <string name="label_us_citizen">I am a U.S. Citizen</string>
    <string name="label_eighteen_or_older">I will be 18 or older by the next election</string>
    <string name="label_has_id">I have a driver\'s license or state ID card.</string>
    <string name="label_first_time_voter">I am registering to vote for the first time</string>
    <string name="label_name_prefix">Title</string>
    <string name="label_first_name">First Name</string>
    <string name="label_middle_name">Middle Name</string>
    <string name="label_last_name">Last Name</string>
    <string name="label_name_suffix">Suffix</string>
    <string name="label_suffix">Suffix</string>

    <string name="label_birthday">Birthday</string>
    <string name="section_label_eligibility">Eligibility</string>
    <string name="section_label_basic_info">Basic Info</string>
    <string name="section_label_new_registrant">New Registrant</string>
    <string name="eighteen_or_older_err">You must be 18 or older to vote</string>
    <string name="us_citizen_err">You must be a U.S. citizen</string>
    <string name="email_error">Invalid email</string>


    <!--Personal Information Strings-->
    <string name="fragment_title_personal_info">Address</string>
    <string name="section_label_personal_info">Address Information</string>
    <string name="section_label_name">Name</string>
    <string name="section_label_previous_name">Previous Name</string>
    <string name="section_label_registration_address">Residential Address</string>
    <string name="section_label_mailing_address">Mailing Address</string>
    <string name="section_label_previous_address">Previous Address</string>
    <string name="section_label_phone">Phone</string>
    <string name="label_street">Street Address</string>
    <string name="label_city">City</string>
    <string name="label_zip_code">Zip Code</string>
    <string name="label_state">State</string>
    <string name="label_unit_num" translatable="false">Unit Type &amp; Number</string>
    <string name="label_county">County</string>
    <string name="checkbox_mailing_address_is_different"> I get my mail from a different address from the one above</string>
    <string name="checkbox_address_changed">I have changed my address</string>
    <string name="checkbox_name_changed">I have changed my name</string>
    <string name="label_receive_text">I agree that %s/Pennsylvania Voice/State Voices may call and text me with important updates and reminders</string>
    <string name="county_empty_error">County Required</string>
    <string name="label_no_address">I have no permanent or mailing address</string>
    <string name="error_no_address">Complete registration using paper form</string>
    <string name="zip_code_error">Invalid zip–code</string>

    <!--Register Fragment Strings-->
    <string name="fragment_title_additional_info">Personal</string>
    <string name="fragment_title_assistant_info">Assistance</string>
    <string name="section_label_gender">Gender</string>
    <string name="section_label_race">Race</string>
    <string name="section_label_party">Political Party</string>
    <string name="section_label_verification">Verification</string>
    <string name="label_male">male</string>
    <string name="label_female">female</string>
    <string name="signature_description">sign here</string>
    <string name="label_button_register">Register</string>
    <string name="label_agreement_prefix">I have read the \u0020</string>
    <string name="label_agreement_link">Voter Registration Agreement</string>
    <string name="agreement_neutral_button">done</string>
    <string name="voter_registration_agreement_title">Voter Registration Agreement</string>

    <!--Additional Info Strings-->
    <string name="label_preferred_language">Preferred Language</string>
    <string name="label_drivers_license_id">PennDOT number</string>
    <string name="label_other_party">Other Political Party</string>
    <string name="label_does_not_have_penn_dot">I do not know my PennDOT number</string>
    <string name="label_ssn_last_four">SSN Last Four</string>
    <string name="label_does_not_have_ssn">I do not know the last four of my SSN</string>
    <string name="preferred_language_label">Preferred Language to Receive Election Materials</string>
    <string name="section_label_election_info">Election Info</string>
    <string name="penn_dot_enforcer_text">If you have a PA driver\'s license or PennDOT ID card number, you must use it</string>
    <string name="error_penn_dot">Check \"I do not know\" if you don\'t know your PennDOT number</string>
    <string name="ssn_enforcer_text">If you do not have a PennDOT number please enter the last 4 digits of your Social Security number </string>
    <string name="error_ssn">Check \"I do not know\" if you don\'t know your SSN last four</string>
    <string name="label_has_assistant">Did someone help you with this form?</string>
    <string name="section_label_assistant_name">Helper Name</string>
    <string name="section_label_assistant_address">Helper Address</string>
    <string name="section_label_assistant_contact_info">Helper Contact Info</string>
    <string name="phone_format_error">Invalid phone number</string>
    <string name="label_email">Email Address</string>
    <string name="label_phone">Phone Number</string>
    <string name="label_phone_type">Type</string>
    <string name="label_receive_email">"I give permission to %s to send me news and updates</string>
    <string name="preferred_language_default">English</string>
    <string name="label_email_confirmation">
    Submit your e-mail address to allow the PA Department of State to send you a message confirming the receipt of your voter registration application:
    \n
    \n
    \u2022 Please note that this email may take up to 24 hours to get to you."
    </string>
    <string name="label_assistant_declaration">
If you helped a voter complete this voter registration application, you must also sign the application.
By checking the box, you are signing the application electronically.
\n
\n
In doing so:
\n
\n
\u2022 You understand that your electronic signature on this application will constitute the legal equivalent of your signature
\n
\n
\u2022 You agree to sign this application by electronic means and that all laws of the Commonwealth of Pennsylvania will apply.
    </string>
    <string name="label_assistant_confirmation">I CONFIRM THAT I HAVE READ AND AGREE TO THE TERMS ABOVE</string>

    <!--Review and Confirm Fragment Strings-->
    <string name="fragment_title_review">Review</string>
    <string name="voter_agreement_text">I have reviewed the above information, and it is true and accurate to the best of my knowledge.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="section_label_contact_info">Contact Info</string>
    <string name="review_confirm_instructions">Please review the following information and confirm its accuracy.</string>
    <string name="section_label_signature">Signature</string>
    <string name="signature_instructions">Please use stylus for signature capture</string>
    <string name="signature_pad_error">Signature is required</string>
    <string name="action_cancel_reg">Cancel Registration</string>
    <string name="registration_complete">Registration Complete</string>
    <string name="disclosure_agreement_title">Voter Declaration / Penalty</string>
    <string name="registration_complete_dialog_text">
\n
\u2022 Your application has been sent to your county voter registration office.
\n
\n
\u2022 Registration is not complete until processed and accepted.
\n
\n
\u2022 If accepted, you will receive a Voter Registration Card by mail.
\n
\n
\u2022 If you do not receive your Voter Registration Card within 14 days, contact your county voter registration office.
\n
\n
Deadline Alert: 10/11/2016 close of registration date of current election is the last day to register before the 11/8/2016 election.
    </string>
    <string name="disclosure_agreement">
<![CDATA[

<p>
I declare that
</p>
<ol >
<li>
I am a United States citizen and will have been a citizen for at least 1 month on the day of the next election.
</li>
<li>
I will be at least 18 years old on the day of the next election.
</li>
<li>
I will have lived at this address for at least 30 days before the election.
</li>
<li>
I am legally qualified to vote.
</li>
</ol >
<p>
I affirm that this information is true. I understand that this declaration is the same as an affidavit, and, if this information is not true, I can be convicted of perjury, and fined up to $15,000, jailed for up to 7 years, or both.

By clicking \'accept\' below, you are signing the application electronically. In doing so:
<p>
<ol>
<li>
You agree you have read and accept the terms of the declaration above.
</li>
<li>
You understand that your electronic signature on this application will constitute the legal equivalent of your signature for this voter registration application.
</li>
<li>
You agree to conduct this voter registration transaction by electronic means and that all laws of the Commonwealth of Pennsylvania will apply to this transaction.
</li>
</ol>
<p>
If you provided your PA driver\'s license or PennDOT ID number, you understand that the signature from the PennDOT record will constitute your signature on your voter registration record. If you upload an image of your signature, you understand that the signature you upload will constitute your signature on your voter registration record. You understand that you do not have to register electronically, and may use a paper or other non-electronic form of this voter registration application.
</p>
<p>
PENALTY FOR FALSIFYING DECLARATION
</p>
<p>
WARNING: If a person signs an official registration application knowing a statement declared in the application to be false, makes a false registration, or furnishes false information, the person commits perjury. Perjury is punishable, upon conviction, by a term of imprisonment not exceeding seven years, or a fine not exceeding $15,000, or both, at the discretion of the court.
</p>
<p>
Submitting an application containing false information may also subject a person to other penalties, including loss of the right of suffrage, under state or federal law.
</p>
]]>
    </string>

    <!-- Preference Strings -->
    <string name="pref_key_partner_id" translatable="false">partner_id</string>
    <string name="pref_key_partner_name" translatable="false">partner_name</string>
    <string name="pref_key_canvasser_name" translatable="false">canvasser_name</string>
    <string name="pref_key_event_zip_code" translatable="false">event_zip</string>
    <string name="pref_key_event_name" translatable="false">event_name</string>
    <string name="pref_key_event_reg_total" translatable="false">event_reg_total</string>
    <string name="pref_key_app_reg_total" translatable="false">app_reg_total</string>

    <string name="pref_title_partner_name" translatable="false">Partner Name</string>
    <string name="pref_title_partner_id" translatable="false">Partner ID</string>
    <string name="pref_title_canvaser_name" translatable="false">Canvaser Name</string>
    <string name="pref_title_event_zip_code" translatable="false">Event Zip Code</string>
    <string name="pref_title_event_name" translatable="false">Event Name</string>

    <!--Multi use strings-->
    <string name="action_cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="action_save">Save</string>
    <string name="action_ok">OK</string>
    <string name="action_accept">Accept</string>
    <string name="action_decline">Decline</string>

    <string name="upload_notification_title_success" translatable="false">PA Registration Success</string>
    <string name="upload_notification_title_failure" translatable="false">PA Registration Failed</string>
    <string name="upload_notification_content_success" translatable="false">Registration submitted</string>
    <string name="upload_notification_content_client_failure" translatable="false">Bad registration data</string>
    <string name="upload_notification_content_connection_failure" translatable="false">Unable to contact server</string>

    <string name="about_activity_text" translatable="false">
<![CDATA[

<p>
&nbsp&nbsp&nbsp&nbsp This mobile application “app” was built by Rock the Vote and OSET’s TrustTheVote Project
to facilitate the submission of electronic voter registration applications in the Commonwealth of
Pennsylvania. It is an extension of Rock the Vote’s national, open source, online voter registration
platform. All Rock the Vote partners using the app are bound by its
<a href="https://www.rockthevote.com/get-involved/register-voters/">Terms of Use</a>
and the
<a href="http://www.dos.pa.gov/VotingElections/OtherServicesEvents/Pages/PA-Online-Voter-Registration-Web-API---RFC.aspx">Terms of Services </a>
outlined by the Pennsylvania Secretary of State’s office
</p>
<p>
&nbsp&nbsp&nbsp&nbsp Rock the Vote is the largest nonpartisan, nonprofit organization in the country driving the
youth vote to the polls. Since 1990, Rock the Vote has fused pop culture, music, art and technology
to fulfill its mission of building long-term youth political power. During the past six Presidential
elections, Rock the Vote ran the largest voter registration drives for young people and has
partnered with more than 25,000 partners through its online, multilingual voter registration
platform.
</p>
<p>
&nbsp&nbsp&nbsp&nbsp The TrustTheVote Project is an initiative of the OSET Foundation, Inc., a tax-exempt 501©(3)
nonprofit California public benefit corporation. It is focused on advancing electoral technology
innovation to improve the voting experience and increase the integrity of elections and their
outcomes.
</p>
<h5>
<a href="grommet://com.rockthevote.grommet/licenses">Open Source Licenses</a>
</h5>
]]>
    </string>

     <string name="data_usage_activity_text" translatable="false">
<![CDATA[

<p>
&nbsp&nbsp&nbsp&nbsp Rock the Vote is committed to preserving your privacy and safeguarding your
sensitive information. The following statement describes the general information-gathering and
usage practices of the online voter registration platform powered by Rock the Vote.
</p>
<ol >
<li>All personal information and other unique identifiers submitted in the process of registering
to vote are used to produce the voter registration form for you to send to your local or state
election officials. If you provide a state-issued identification number or Social Security number,
it will be used solely for the production of your voter registration form.
</li>
<li>Once you mail in or electronically submit your voter registration application form to your
local or state election officials, it becomes a matter of public record and is available for
inspection and use by those who satisfy the requirements of the State law governing its use.
</li>
<li>By using the online voter registration platform, you grant Rock the Vote and its online voter
registration partners permission to use your personal contact information to send you
communications. Rock the Vote is bound by its
<a href="https://www.rockthevote.com/about-us/privacy-policy.html">privacy policy</a>.
All entities using the Rock the Vote online voter registration tool are bound to act in accordance
with their privacy policies. You can unsubscribe at any time by following the unsubscribe
instructions on the communication itself.
</li>
<li>Rock the Vote may track information on where its online voter registration platform is being
visited and used so we can make decisions about the design and usage of the online voter
registration tool.
</li>
<li>Whenever Rock the Vote handles information that you enter on the online voter registration
platform, regardless of where this occurs, we take steps to ensure that your information is treated
securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the
Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal
information, Rock the Vote cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to
us and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to
ensure its security on our systems.
</li>
</ol>

]]>
    </string>

    <string name="help_activity_text" translatable="false">
<![CDATA[
<p>
&nbsp&nbsp&nbsp&nbsp If you have any questions about this app or its data usage policy please contact
<a href="mailto:info@rockthevote.com">info@rockthevote.com<a/>.
</p>
<p>
&nbsp&nbsp&nbsp&nbsp To get started using this app as a partner, you must first sign-up to be a
<a href="https://vr.rockthevote.com/partner/register">Rock the Vote partner</a>.
Any interested partners must be approved to use the canvasser app.
</p>
]]>
    </string>

</resources>
